Finding Aid for the Lisa See Papers LSC.0564
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings by Lisa See
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 14 Sep 1990; 28 Sep 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    "Turan to Be Temporary Editor of 'L.A. Times Book Review'" (p. 10); "Works by Native American Writers Find Wider Audience" (p. 80).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 2 Nov 1990; 9 Nov 1990; 16 Nov 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    "Northern California Booksellers" (p. 32, with John Mutter) and "Harper, Hazelden Renew Recovery Bond for Six Years (p. 44); "Kate Braverman" (p. 42); "Hearst on Hearst From Roberts Rinehart" (p. 35).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 7 Dec 1990; 21 Dec 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    "10,000 Celebrate Bay Area Book Festival ..." (p. 18), "The Epicenter Holds" (p. 38), "Honoring Writers - and Publishers - in L.A." (p. 56), and "Putnam's 'In the Absence of Angels' ... (p. 40); "How the Book World in the West Was Won" (p. 34).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 3 Jan 1986; 31 Jan 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    "In Gardening Books -- and Now Cookbooks -- Ortho Has the Numbers" (p. 40); "Activism Is Still Alive and Well in Northern California" (p. 340).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 7 Mar 1986; 28 Mar 1986; 25 Apr 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    "Spreading the Word" (p. 36) and "Elizabeth Forsythe Hailey" (p. 80); "Women on the Move: Three Success Stories" (p. 26); "Writers and Publishers in Search Of the Chinese Experience" (p. 42).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 30 May 1986; 18 Jul 1986; 1 Aug 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    "Chronicle Books ..." (p. 38), "Are Video and Satellite Services an Alternative ..." (p. 44), and "Regional Cooperation" (p. 46); "Educational Marketer Learns the Retail Ropes" (p. 54); "Arion: Making Fine Books (Ultimately) for the Masses" (p. 54).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 12 Sep 1986; 26 Sep 1986; 14 Nov 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    "Jerome Weidman" (p. 72); "California Dreams: A Soap Opera Scrapbook, Personified Qualities, Literary Maps" (p. 56); "California Meeting Sticks to Its Working Show Tradition (p. 44) and "Celebration at Cody's Books" (p. 45).
  - Publishers Weekly, 11 Jul 1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Issue of "Publishers Weekly" in which Lisa See is listed in the masthead, but with no author attribution within the publication. Inside issue are photocopies of reviews, notices, etc., for "110 Shanghai Road".
  - Publishers Weekly, 4 Apr 1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Issue of "Publishers Weekly" in which Lisa See is listed in the masthead, but with no author attribution within the publication. Advertisement for "110 Shanghai Road" on p. 6.
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 8 Mar 1991; 15 Mar 1991; 22 Mar 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    "Interim Editor Discusses Changes at 'L.A. Times Book Review'" (p. 10); "Prima Grows Fast Four Ways" (p. 9); "Flying Spur Press: Phoenix Arising from the Flames" (p. 18).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 5 Apr 1991; 26 Apr 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    "The Hollywood Connection" (p. 8); "BABRA Honors North Point Press at 10th Annual Awards Ceremony" (p. 14).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 10 May 1991; 31 May 1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    "Slawson Names Fisher President, Buys Publishers Marketing Services" (p. 102) and "Fresno, Calif., Meeting Launches Awards for Popular Fiction" (p. 108); "Sinatra Lawyer Sues Kitty Kelley Over Listing in Acknowledgements" (p.25).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 21 Jun 1991; 19 Jul 1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    "In California, New Faces & Old Hands Turn to the Environment" (p. 29); "Owner Shuts Down Bedford Arts; Nine on Staff Lose Jobs" (p. 6) and "California and Princeton Presses to Combine Fulfillment Operations" (p. 10).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 9 Aug 1991; 16 Aug 1991; 13 Sep 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    "Sierra Club Books Cuts Jobs and Adult Trade Titles" (p. 12) and "Championing the Freedom to Read" (p. 29); "The First Pitch at SportsBooks" (p. 28); "California Lowers Rates on Worker's Compensation" (p. 8).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 20 Sep 1991; 4 Oct 1991; 11 Oct 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    "11 Bay Area Stores Reject Censure ..." (p. 17) and "From 'A Day in the Life' to ..." (p. 41); "Bolle to Head 'L.A. Times Book Review'; ..." (p. 11) and "Price Stern Sloan President to Leave ..." (p. 13); "U.C. Press Gets Okay ..." (p. 13).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 18 Oct 1991; 8 Nov 1991; 29 Nov 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    "Second Sacramento Book Fair Raises $18,000 for Literacy" (p. 16); "Mountains and Plains Booksellers" (p. 38); "Bay Area Book People Revel in Second Annual Festival" (p. 15) and "Going West" (p. 17).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 24 Feb 1992; 9 Mar 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    "Mexican House Plans to Publish Spanish Titles for U.S. Market" (p.10); "AMS Sales Improve, to Publishers' Relief (p. 6, with John F. Baker).
  - Publishers Weekly, 4 Jan 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 4 May 1992; 11 May 1992; 25 May 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    "Publishers Group West Hits Stride; 1991 Sales Up 25%" (p.12); "Ingram's PRI Joins Prima in New Marketing Venture" (p. 7).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 8 Jun 1992; 29 Jun 1992; 6 Jul 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    "Where the Big Deals Are" (p. 26); "Paul Monette" (p. 42); "Anatomy of Two Children's Bookstore Closings" (p. 13) and Griffin & Sabine's Continued Correspondence at Chronicle" (p. 17).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 3 Aug 1992; 10 Aug 1992; 7 Sep 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    "Cynthia Kadohata" (p. 48); "A New Business Concept from a New Business Publisher" (p. 22); "Prima Distribution Venture Put on Hold for Two Years" (p. 12) and "Berry Gordy, Carol Publishing Author Sue and Counter-sue" (p. 13).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 12 Oct 1992; 26 Oct 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    "California Style" (p. 32); "Bay Area Rumblings: The Recession and Superstores" (p. 16, with Maria Heidkamp).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 16 Nov 1992; 30 Nov 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    "Staff at Cody's Bookstore Votes to Organize" (p. 12) "New $50,000 Award for Poetry" (p. 12), and "Pfeiffer's Business Books Enter the Trade" (p. 22); "Midnight Special Moves, Opens Cultural Center" (p. 14).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 14 Dec 1992; 28 Dec 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    "New NCBA Director" (p. 21); "Timely Project Documents Life 'n the Hood" (p. 25) and "How Fondo de Cultura Is Seeding the U.S. Market" (p. 44).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 11 Jan 1993; 18 Jan 1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    "Dove Inks Deal for Spanish Audio" (p. 8); "'Flexible Network' of Small Presses Launched in Oregon" (p. 16) and "Nonprofit Small Press Wholesaler Grows; Looks to Fundraising" (p. 17).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 25 Jan 1993; 8 Feb 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    "The Reactions to Colorado's Anti-Gay Amendment" (p. 20) and "For Women Only" (p. 38); "'50 Simple Things' Publisher Jumps into the Clinton Era with New Title" (p. 10).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 1 Mar 1993; 22 Mar 1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    "Customer Roundup on Rodeo Drive" (p. 16); "Steve Erickson" (p. 59).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 24 May 1993; 31 May 1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    "Bookshop Santa Cruz Regains Its Footing" (p. 36); "Atrium Is America's Fastest-Growing Distributor" (p. 12).
  - Publishers Weekly, 22 Feb 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 21 Jun 1993; 28 Jun 1993; 5 Jul 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    "Barbara Wood/Kathryn Harvey" (p. 76); "Hunter House Wins Award" (p. 16); "Publishers, Authors, Movie Stars Help L.A. Public Reopen" (p. 18).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 2 Aug 1993; 16 Aug 1993; 4 Oct 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    "PEN Center West Protests Massive Cuts in L.A. Library System" (p. 12); "Reports from the Field" (p. 30); "Independents Go on the Air" (p. 20).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 1 Nov 1993; 8 Nov 1993; 29 Nov 1993; 13 Dec 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    "How Newton Came to Be" (p. 26); "Merrill Joan Gerber" (p. 54); "Surprise Bestseller Boosts Small Alaskan House" (p. 16) and "Fast-Growing S.F. House Honored (p. 20); "Octavia E. Butler" (p. 50).
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of "110 Shanghai Road"; outline; description of major characters. Includes "Prologue" numbered 1-67; "Book I" numbered 68-149; "Book II" numbered 1- 5; "Book IV" numbered 31-52; "Book V" numbered 53-82; "Book VI" numbered 83- 112.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK III"; pages numbered from 1-95.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK II"; pages numbered from 1-42. After last page, two handwritten pages.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK I"; pages numbered from 68-149.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 166, and goes through page 181. At top of following page is "Book VI"; pages numbered 1-9.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 77, and goes through page 165.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 38, and goes through page 76.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 117, and goes through page 175. At top of following page is "Book V"; pages numbered 1-37.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 17, and goes through page 116.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". First page numbered 41, and goes through page 103. At top of following page is "Book IV"; pages numbered 1-16.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". Title page has title as "Shanghai". Contains Books II (numbered 1-5), III (numbered 6-30), IV (numbered 31-52), and VI (numbered 83-112).
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK III"; pages numbered 1-95.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK V"; pages numbered 53-82.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Three pages of handwritten notes for "110 Shanghai Road".
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book VI"; pages numbered 83-112.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book II"; pages numbered 1-42.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book II"; pages numbered 1-49. After this section, at top of page is "Book III"; pages numbered 1-40.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book VI". Pages numbered 1-97. Includes a checklist for writing, typing, revising, etc., of manuscript; part of original folder with notes.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Prologue". Pages numbered 1-67. After last page, four handwritten pages.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book V". Pages numbered 1-169 ("168" and "169" are handwritten). Inserted among typewritten pages are handwritten pages.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book IV". Pages numbered 1-160. Inserted among typewritten pages are handwritten pages. Includes part of original folder with notes.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 29, Folder 5)
    One typewritten page; one handwritten page for "110 Shanghai Road". Typewritten page is title page for "Shanghai" by Monica Highland; handwritten page contains lists and a quote by Shanghai Lily.
  - Book- Lotus Land (1 of 5) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Five typewritten pages of "Notes" on "Prologue" through "Book VI" for "Lotus Land".
  - Book- Lotus Land (2 of 5) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript of "Lotus Land". Pages 699-701; 720-722; 733-746; 757-763.
  - Book- Lotus Land (3 of 5) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Typewritten manuscript of "Lotus Land". Pages 691-698; 705-709; 723-730; 765-772.
  - Book- Lotus Land (4 of 5) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Typewritten manuscript of "Lotus Land". Title page; dedication page; page with "PROLOGUE: 1881-1885" at the top and a quote from "The Odyssey"; pages 1- 131.
  - Book- Lotus Land (5 of 5) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript of "Lotus Land". Very little editing. "BOOK I", pages 132-174; 183-186; 194-246. "BOOK II", pages 247-306; 323-335. "BOOK III", page 336.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (1 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Prologue". Pages numbered 1-3; 7-39; 5; 40-69. Inserted among typewritten pages are unnumbered pages with handwritten and/or typewritten text.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (2 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book I". Pages numbered 1-3; 5-29; 30-68; 46; 69-82. Inserted among typewritten pages are unnumbered pages with handwritten and/or typewritten text.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (3 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book II". Pages numbered 1-39.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (4 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "BOOK III". Pages numbered 1-82.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (5 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book IV". Pages numbered 1-144. Some page numbers corrected in pencil. Inserted among typewritten pages are handwritten pages.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (6 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book V". Pages numbered 1-43; 45; 44; 47-161.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (7 of 7) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". At top of first page is "Book VI". Pages numbered 1-80.
  - Lotus Land IV-VI [1 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "Lotus Land". Many pages are not full-size, but cut into smaller sections of text. Two pages of handwritten notes among typewritten pages. Many page numbers out of sequence.
  - Lotus Land IV-VI [2 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "Lotus Land". At top of first page is "BOOK IV". Pages numbered 462; 475;499; 506-537; 540-541; 556-562.
  - Lotus Land IV-VI [3 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "Lotus Land". At top of first page is "BOOK V". Pages numbered 566-680.
  - Lotus Land IV-VI [4 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "Lotus Land". At top of first page is "BOOK VI". Pages numbered 681-690; 702-704; 710-719; 731-732; 747-756; 764; 773- 809.
  - Cosmetic Surgery, Etc., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Untitled manuscripts on various subjects; papers for CA 420 course at Loyola Marymount University. Also includes correspondence; biographical information on Jacqueline Hansen; letter from Manolis Andreasson.
  - Articles- TV Guide, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Correspondence sent from the "TV Guide" Reader's Service relating to articles "And You Thought Big Macs Were Fast Food" and "Watch Out! Sometimes Stinky Bites!"
  - Screenplay- Secrets, 5 Oct 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript of "Secrets" by Lisa See and Carolyn See. Includes title page and pages 1-108.
  - SECOND CHANCE [1 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of the screenplay "Secrets". Pages numbered 1-20; 22; 24-36; 38-51; 54-62 (two pages numbered "62", one typed, one handwritten); 66-78; 77 (second page to be numbered "77"); 82-91; 89 (second page to be numbered "89"); 93- 103.
  - SECOND CHANCE [2 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of the screenplay "Secrets". Pages numbered 1-110. On last page is "A+".
  - SECOND CHANCE [3 of 3], 1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscripts, edited, of the screenplay "Secrets"; outlines; rewrite notes from Barry Krost and Carla Singer. Also includes correspondence with Tri-Star Pictures, Inc. and Warner Bros. Television; articles on sex offenders and child abuse.
  - Shanghai/Book II [1 of 5] (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Handwritten manuscript, on a notepad, of "110 Shanghai Road". Pages numbered 1-107.
  - Shanghai/Book II [2 of 5], 25 Oct 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript of "110 Shanghai Road", copyright Warner Bros. Inc. On cover is "110 SHANGHAI ROAD PART ONE". Treatment by Jeb Rosebrook; story by Jeb Rosebrook and Joe Byrne.
  - Shanghai/Book II [3 of 5], 25 Oct 1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript of "110 Shanghai Road", copyright Warner Bros. Inc. On cover is "110 SHANGHAI ROAD PART TWO". Treatment by Jeb Rosebrook; story by Jeb Rosebrook and Joe Byrne.
  - Shanghai/Book II [4 of 5], 25 Oct 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of "110 Shanghai Road", copyright Warner Bros. Inc. On cover is "110 SHANGHAI ROAD PART THREE". Treatment by Jeb Rosebrook; story by Jeb Rosebrook and Joe Byrne.
  - Shanghai/Book II [5 of 5] (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Handwritten manuscript on a notepad, extensively edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". Pages numbered 2-31.
  - SHANGHAI (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Handwritten manuscript on notepads, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". Sections entitled "1926" (pages 1-27); "1939" (pages 1-19); "1944" (pages 1-22 and 26-27); "1950- 57" (pages 1-28); "1967" (pages 1-38); "1983" (pages 1-38 and 40-45).
  - SHANGHAI BOOK I (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Handwritten manuscript on notepads, edited, of "110 Shanghai Road". Pages numbered 80-97, followed by 1-79, in reverse order.
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 3 Apr 1987; 12 Jun 1987; 25 Dec 1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    "Big Books, Small Screen" (p. 26) and "Opportunities Abound on PBS and Cable" (p. 30); "Tube Power" (p. 49); "40 to Lose Jobs When Hunters in Westwood, Beverly Hills Close" (p. 23) and "A Book Award for Independent Publishers" (p. 51).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 22 Jan 1988; 29 Jan 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    "'L.A. Times' Drops Mass Market, Trade PBs from Bestseller Lists" (p. 18); "The End of an L.A. Bookselling Era" (p. 409).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 26 Feb 1988; 25 Mar 1988; 29 Apr 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    "Thinking Big: 'Mission Earth' in Paperback" (p. 175); "NewSage Press: Photography Books with Vision" (p. 36); "Heyday Books" (p. 21) and "A Book by -- and for -- the Homeless, Put Together with Help from Many Friends" (p. 45).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly., 13 May 1988; 27 May 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    "A Sampling of Stores" (p. 144) and "Dutton's Books Thrive" (p. 146); "Presidio: Taking Off from a Base of Military Affairs" (p. 26).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 24 Jun 1988; 2 Sep 1988; 30 Sep 1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    "How Westerners Fared at ABA" (p. 44); "Western Publishers Honor John Muir" (p. 82); "Writers of Children's Books Talk About Their Calling" (p. 32), "Art by Noted Children's Book Artists ..." (p. 36) and "Knapp: Feasts for the Eyes and the Table" (p. 38).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 28 Oct 1988; 25 Nov 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    "A 'New' San Francisco Review" (p. 58); "Thom Gunn Wins Kirsch Award" (p. 13), "A Field Day for Booksellers" (p. 42), "Fisher Books: Back to Life After HP" (p. 52), and "Sydney Sheldon" (p. 53).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 23 Dec 1988; 27 Jan 1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    "Tale Weaver and Movie Firm Promote 'Hollywood Legends'" (p. 53) and "Tudor: A Bi-Coastal Drive for Bestsellerdom" (p. 59); "A State Bonanza for Washington Publishers" (p. 448).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 24 Feb 1989; 24 Mar 1989; 31 Mar 1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    "Green Tiger Bounces Back: A Cautionary Tale" (p. 191); "YYR Conference Draws Large Turnout, Provokes Discussion" (p. 41) and "A. Scott Berg" (p. 49); "Bringing West Coast History Back to Life" (p. 33).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 7 Apr 1989; 28 Apr 1989; 26 May 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    "Los Angeles-Based AIDS Project Gives First Literary Awards" (p. 38); "Avoiding New York Publishers ..." (p. 55); "A Bookstore Older Than the Movies" (p. 33) and "Publishers Group West: Small Press Distributor Hits the Big Time" (p. 40).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 23 Jun 1989; 30 Jun 1989; 28 Jul 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    "Books for Art's Sake" (p. 40); "Bebe Moore Campbell" (p. 82); "Talk-Show Prep" (p. 201).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 25 Aug 1989; 1 Sep 1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    "ACLU Asks Probe of 'Harassment' of Los Angeles Bookstore" (p. 11); "Battle to Keep a Bookstore in Town" (p. 66).
  - Flower Net Outline (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscripts one of which is entitled "The Flower Net Proposal by Lisa See"; two others entitled "The Flower Net Working Outline General Overview".
  - The Flower Net (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Four typewritten manuscripts entitled "The Flower Net Proposal by Lisa See"; another entitled "Prologue January 4 Outside Beijing"; another entitled "Chapter 2 February 4 Los Angeles".
  - Book- The Flower Net, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Folder from the Sandra Dijkstra Literary Agency containing a proposal, prologue, and chapters one and two for "The Flower Net"; author biography; photocopies of articles, bestseller lists, and reviews for "On Gold Mountain".
  - The Flower Net (etc.), 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Articles from "Daily Variety", "San Diego Home/Garden lifestyles", and "Publishing News" relating to movie development and auction for publishing rights for "The Flower Net" and "On Gold Mountain".
  - The Flower Net, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Correspondence relating to purchase of film rights to "The Flower Net"; "Publishers Weekly" issue with article on "The Flower Net" auction at the Frankfurt Fair (p. 23); "Daily Variety" article on purchase of film rights (p. 3).
  - The Interior - Proposal, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Three manuscripts entitled "The Interior Proposal" (one of which has facsimiles from Sandra Dijkstra attached to it); four entitled "Prologue"; one entitled "The Interior"; one entitled "CHAPTER 1".
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (1 of 4) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Title page through Chapter 6.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (2 of 4) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Chapters 7- 12.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (3 of 4) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Chapters 13- 19.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (4 of 4) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Chapter 20 through "Sources".
  - Book- The Interior, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Bound galleys of "The Interior".
  - Book- The Interior (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "The Interior".